singsaver.com.sg 2018-09-27

# Privacy Policy | SingSaver

## SingSaver.com.sg Privacy Policy

SingSaver.com.sg is owned and operated by SingSaver Pte. Ltd. ("SingSaver"). The following Privacy Policy protects your personal data in compliance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (PDPA) ("The Act"). This Privacy Policy explains the way we will collect, use and disclose your personal data and the measures taken to ensure that your data stays secure and confidential.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, whenever we use "us", "we" and "our", it refers to SingSaver and "you" and "your" refers to anyone who uses SingSaver.com.sg (the ?Website?).

## Collection of Personal Information

During the course of registration for and/or using our services (for example, to get comparative quotes for personal loans), we may collect some of your Personal Data. We might also store data concerning how you use our Website, for instance, the website from which you come from to reach our Website, the pages you view, changes you make to the data provided to us, details of the quotes you request and your transactions.

In this Privacy Policy, the term "Personal Data" means data, whether true or not, about an individual who can be identified from that data; or from that data and other information to which SingSaver has or is likely to have access.

The Personal Data we may ask you to provide includes (without limitation):

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Telephone number
  * Age (birth date)
  * Dependents
  * Nationality
  * Any messages if you write to us using the "contact us" form
  * Your saving goals
  * Your residency status/details
  * Your income
  * Details of the products you are looking for (for example, the size of loan)
  * Passport number, NRIC number and/or FIN
  * Education history
  * Assets
  * Employment status and details
  * Employer or company details
  * Whether you have an existing relationship with the bank you are applying to
  * US tax residency status
  * Senior Public Figure Declaration
  * Payment details (when purchasing a product)
  * Information related to any of the above

In addition, when you use the Website, we may automatically collect certain data which may, when combined with other information about you, constitute Personal Data. For example:

  * attributes of the equipment or device you are using, such as the operating system, hardware version, device settings, software and device identifiers;
  * device locations, including specific geographic locations identified through GPS, Bluetooth or WiFi signals or other means;
  * connection information such as the name of your mobile operator, ISP or other service provider, browser type and IP address;
  * the website from which you have reached the Website;
  * the Website pages viewed;
  * details of the products and services on the site that you look at, information, tools and content available on our site that you use;
  * links from our site that you click on;
  * quotes you request from our Website;
  * your transactions on our Website and details of any payments made by you (including bank account and credit card details and any other account identification information); and
  * information related to any of the above.

## Purposes For Which We Use Your Data

Personal information collected online will only be disclosed:

  * Within our corporate group;
  * to third party service providers who are banks, brokers, lenders and other money and financial service providers whose products may be displayed on our Website from time to time (including their related companies outside of Singapore) and their service providers ("Bank Partners"); and
  * otherwise as required by law.

The personal information we collect from you may be used in some or all of the following ways:

  * to allow you to access and use our free comparison services;
  * to direct your enquiry to one of our Bank Partners or related partners;
  * to provide you with relevant product information;
  * to enable Bank Partners to contact and assist you if you express interest in their products or services;
  * to enable you to access online application forms on third party external sites;
  * to improve our overall service to you and other users, to analyse market trends and client demographics;
  * to send you information concerning products and services which you may have expressed an interest in;
  * to assist in the application for a particular product or service from a Service Provider;
  * to complete your registration on our Website;
  * to contact you regarding any complaints, feedback, queries or requests;
  * to facilitate investigation into any suspicious or illegal activity on the Website;
  * for internal administrative and management purposes;
  * where required by any act, statute, law, or regulation, or by the order
  * of a government authority or a court or tribunal of competent jurisdiction;
  * such other purposes for which your consent has been obtained;
  * to allow you to log into your personalized account on the Website; and/or
  * any other purpose reasonably related to the aforesaid.

You hereby represent and warrant that the Personal Data provided to us is true and accurate and undertake to notify us of any change or alteration to the same. You will be responsible for any loss or damage caused to the Website or to any third person through the provision of erroneous, inexact or incomplete information.

When you sign in or subscribe at SingSaver.com.sg, we may use the personal information you provide to us to send/contact you regarding marketing and/or promotional materials from time to time. We will not use your Personal Data for direct marketing without your prior consent. Where relevant, we will allow our affiliates, subsidiaries and/or related companies to send relevant marketing materials to you, but will always obtain your consent before doing so.

We will always give you the liberty, at any time, to unsubscribe from marketing information by using the unsubscribe function within the electronic marketing material.

## Disclosure of Personal Data

We will keep your personal data confidential and not disclose or transfer such information to or allow access by any party except as follows.

In connection with the above purposes, we may share your Personal Data with:

  * our affiliates in the CompareAsiaGroup that provide services to, or share services with, SingSaver;
  * Bank Partners; and
  * other service providers that support our business, for example (without limitation) our IT and analytics service providers, back office support, business consultants, legal service providers and marketing service providers.

We and/or any of the third parties listed above may also be required to disclose your Personal Data to any court, law enforcement body, government department, regulator or industry body of any country where required by the laws of Singapore or any other jurisdiction, or in response to a lawful request in Singapore or elsewhere. We may also need to disclose your Personal Data to identify, contact or bring legal action against any person who may be causing damage to or interfere with our and/or any third party's rights or property (whether intentionally or otherwise).

## Keeping You Updated Regarding Our Services

From time to time, we may inform you via email, post, phone calls or by text of products, services and other offers we expect could be of interest to you.

## Improving Our Service

In order to ensure that the services we offer you continue to meet your requirements, we might ask for your feedback. Any feedback you give us will solely be used to improve our services to you and shall not be revealed on the Website.

## Third Party Providers and Privacy of Information

If you opt to enter into a contract with a Service Provider through this Website, the data you provide to us, along with any other information requested and provided by you or us to the Service Provider are controlled by the third party in accordance with that third-party provider's privacy policy. Thus, we suggest that you go through your chosen Service Provider's privacy policy before entering a contract with them. We are not responsible for how third party providers use your Personal Data.

## Cookies and Collection of Data

We strive to provide you with the best possible service, and to help us do this we record cookies. When users visit the Website, our servers will record information that browsers send. This includes but not limited to:

  * IP Address;
  * Browser type;
  * Website visited before user came to the Website;
  * What page user viewed on the Website; and/or
  * Time spent on the Website

These cookies enable us to:

  * provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website. It allows us to remember you when you revisit this Website. You can also access your previously saved quotes;
  * study browsing habits on this Website. The more we understand what products you are interested in, the greater our ability to offer you customized solutions; and
  * obtain information regarding the number of visitors to this Website and the pages viewed.

In most cases, cookies are deleted when you close your browser; these are referred to as session cookies. However, persistent cookies stay on your browsing device either until such time you delete them or they expire. By using this Website, you consent to us using cookies. Such use of data does not disclose any of your Personal Data, and we will not collect, process or use any of your Personal Data in this regard.

You can alter your computer browser settings to block or delete cookies. If you opt to block or delete cookies of the Website, you may not be able to access certain products or services and this could have an effect on the performance of the Website on your system (for example, banner ads may not display properly).

Using the above, SingSaver.com.sg may use Google Analytics and Google Display Network features including advertising and remarketing. Please visit https://www.google.com/settings/ads if you want to opt out of these features.

## Security, Storage and Retention

Keeping your data secure is important to us. This Website is a "VeriSign Secure Website" and thus offers a high level of data protection. However, no information transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. Highly sensitive data, such as your credit card details, are encrypted to minimise the danger of interception throughout transit. However, while we try our best to safeguard your Personal Data, we cannot assure or warrant the safety of any data that you give us, and you do so at your own risk. We do not accept liability for the security, authenticity, integrity or confidentiality of any transaction and other communications made through the Website.

When you register an account with us, you will be asked to choose a password. It is your responsibility to keep your password safe, and not share it with anyone. We are not responsible for any transactions conducted by a third party that has logged in to your account using your password. If you suspect that your account has been used by someone other than you, please notify us straight away.

All Personal Data that has been collected from you will only be stored for a duration that is relevant to the purpose for which it was processed and for as long as permissible by applicable law(s), in any event no longer than necessary for purposes mentioned in the ?Purposes for which we use your data? section above.

## Your Responsibilities

You may be required to complete a registration process as a part of your use of this Website. This may include the creation of a username and password. You should not disclose your username and password to anyone. If you choose to share your username and password with anyone, you are responsible for all activities undertaken on this Website using your username and password.

## Access to and Correction of Personal Data

You have a right to request access to and correction of your Personal Data held by us in accordance with The Act.

## Language

This privacy policy has originally been drawn up in the English language.

## Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to amend and revise this Privacy Policy at any time without giving prior notification. All changes will be posted on this page, and your access or use of the Website after such changes have been posted will constitute your agreement to the modified Privacy Policy and all of the changes. You should therefore read this page carefully each time you visit this Website.

## Contacting Us About This Policy

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, contact us at:

SingSaver Pte Ltd

1A Keong Saik Rd, Singapore, 089109

Phone: +65 3158 0152 (lines are open Monday to Friday 9.00am to 5.00pm)

Email: info@singsaver.com.sg

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 10 February 2017.
